marciano.com 2010-06-18

# GUESS by Marciano

**At GUESSbyMarciano.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy.** We firmly believe that electronic security and privacy are necessary for the continued success of the Internet. In support of this, we only use the personal information that you provide to create a more personalized and entertaining experience for you, in accordance with the terms outlined below.

**Kids' policy (individuals under 13 years of age).** GUESSbyMarciano.com is committed to protecting the safety of children online. In compliance with the Children's Privacy Protection Act of 1998, GUESSbyMarciano.com will never knowingly request or use personal information from children under 13 years of age without prior parental consent. If GUESSbyMarciano.com receives actual knowledge that a subscriber is under 13 years of age, GUESSbyMarciano.com will eliminate all personal information relating to this subscriber from our files.

Information We Gather

We use all information provided during registration and personalization to provide personalized content and services. Any account information you supply will be used only to process requested commerce transactions or to contact you regarding a specific transaction. GUESSbyMarciano.com may also use this information in order to generate aggregate reports that help us determine how to improve our users' experience. This data is anonymous and does not contain any personally identifiable information. GUESSbyMarciano.com will not disclose your user information to any outside organization without your consent. However, GUESSbyMarciano.com may disclose user information to the government and/or third parties when we have reason to believe that disclosure of such information is necessary to identify or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms and Conditions or otherwise causing harm to GUESSbyMarciano.com or anyone who could be victimized by such activities, and where otherwise required by law or by legal process.

By providing your email, cell phone number and/or telephone number during registration or personalization, you agree to receive marketing (including email, cell phone text messaging, and/or voice messaging) information from Guess, Inc. that informs you of new products, sales, promotions, contests, and features. Depending on the terms of your cell phone calling plan, you may incur, at your sole expense, a charge for received text messages. We may also offer you special promotions from our site or our sponsors. If you prefer not to receive such communications, you may contact us using our 

. We also use third party service providers to communicate with our customers and to do some promotions. We do not, however, authorize any of these service providers to make any other use of your information.

GUESSbyMarciano.com also derives user information through some simple technical methods. We may use data-tracking software that lets us know what areas of the site you visit most often. This helps us present you with the information and features in which you are most interested.

We may use your IP (Internet protocol) address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

Security

Providing a safe and secure environment for your order information is our top priority. GUESSbyMARCIANO.com protects the security of your online transaction by taking advantage of Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. The MARCIANO Online Store uses digital certificates provided by Equifax which are required for SSL, the industry standard for encryption. SSL technology encrypts data allowing only MARCIANO to decode your information and helps to create a secure environment for transactions on the internet. To further protect your security, we suggest you sign off your account and close your browser window after you have finished your visit, especially if you are using a computer shared by others.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with GUESSbyMarciano.com, you can contact us:

Customer Service  
GUESSbyMarciano.com  
1444 Alameda St.  
Los Angeles, CA 90021
